Mitchie! Up!
Last day of school!
Whoa
Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah
How to choose who to be
Well. let's see
There's so many choices now
Play guitar. be a movie star
In my head a voice says
Why not try everything?
Why stop? Reach for any dream
I can rock
'Cause it's my life
And now's the time. who will I be?
It's up to me
All the never-ending possibilities
That I can see
There's nothing that I can't do
Who will I be?
Yes. I believe I get to make the future
What I want to
If I can become anyone
And know the choice is up to me
Who will I be?
I wanna find the who I am inside
I wanna show the
The way that I can shine
Who will I be?
Oh. cool. Hot Tunes is on.
Turn it up. please.
The pop star phenom Shane Gray
may have gone too far this time
when he stormed off the set
of the new Connect 3 video.
Word is the other members
of Connect 3 are fed up.
This final stunt cost his label
thousands of dollars.
but may cost them
the rest of their record deal.
What is wrong with that boy?
He's got everything.
Except a clue.
The message is clear.
he needs to clean up his act.
And to give him time to do it.
the Connect 3's summer tour
has been canceled.
Look what I found in the crisper.
A Camp Rock brochure.
Or should I say another
Camp Rock brochure?
Hmm. Look at that.
Oh. and great cheese omelet.
by the way.
You should definitely add that
to your catering menu.
So you have no idea
how this brochure got in there?
Or the one taped
to the vacuum cleaner?
Sweetie. I know you wanna go
to this camp.
And I'm sorry.
but we just can't swing it right now.
With Dad expanding the store
and my catering business
just taking off...
Oh. honey. I'm sorry.
I know.
Got to go.
Last day of school.
Don't want to be late.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
- Hey. Mitchie.
- Hey. Sierra.
Let me be the first to say
Shing Sha Ji. Mitchie.
It means. "Happy summer. Mitchie."
Guess who got an A-plus
in AP Mandarin? Me. Again.
So. how'd it go this morning?
It didn't. Camp Rock is a no-go.
But you have to go.
Camp Rock is. like. the music camp.
Anybody who wants to be somebody
in music...
All of which you already know. Sorry.
Me. too.
I was just so excited to have a summer
that was all about music. And...
I know.
So. what are you going to do
this summer?
So. how was work?
You know Barney's. We serve burgers
with a Barney's smile.
- So what's for dinner?
- Burgers.
Well. our world-famous Torres burger.
Um...
I'll pass.
Okay. I can't stand it. Tell her.
- Well. Steve. she just got home.
- Tell me what?
- Okay. honey. Drum roll.
- Mom?
Okay. You're going to Camp Rock!
- What?
- She said you're going to Camp Rock.
Well. actually. we're going.
Connie's Catering is going camping.
Business is slow in the summer.
this is a steady job.
and you get to go to camp
at a discounted rate!
But you have to help out in the kitchen.
Thank you!
Thank you. like. a million times!
Oh.
- We're here.
- Yeah. Are you excited?
A little. Okay. a lot! Yes! Major!
Thank you. Mom.
I'm gonna have so much fun.
Whoa.
Okay. Sweetie. let's get settled in.
Settled.
That's great. Brown Cesario.
Camp director/founding member
and bass guitar of the White Crows.
And you must be Connie Torres.
our new cook.
That's me.
And this is my daughter.
- Who's already gone.
- No worries.
She probably just wanted
to get out there. get to it.
you know what I mean?
When the music calls.
you got to answer.
I can't wait for you to meet her though.
She has got a great voice.
- Look at me. I'm already bragging.
- Oh. you got to brag. love.
Learned that from the Mickster. Jagger.
You knew Mick Jagger?
Yeah. Backed him up for years.
Great times. great times.
But not as great as the time
- when I toured with Aerosmith.
- You knew Aerosmith?
Sorry. I didn't... I didn't see you.
Obviously.
That's Tess Tyler.
the diva of Camp Rock.
Is she really good?
She's good at trying too hard
to be good.
Understandable.
'cause her mom's TJ Tyler.
The TJ Tyler?
She's got like a trillion Grammys.
A trillion and one. I think.
Hi. I'm Caitlyn.
Camper today.
top-selling music producer tomorrow.
Check me out.
- Cool. I'm Mitchie.
- Hi.
Hi. gang! I'm Dee Le Duke.
the musical director here
at Camp Rock.
Hi. Dee.
Here at Camp Rock we sing.
So let's hear that again.
Hi. Dee
Sounds good. A little pitchy in places.
but we'll fix that by the Final Jam.
Hey! We're here to rock it out
At least I know I am
We plan to be the winners onstage
at Final Jam
-Holler
- Holler
Put your hands up
-Hey. hey
- Come on. everybody
Get your hands up
Okay. okay. Settle down.
You're having too much fun.
Okay. this summer is not just
about the Final Jam.
We have a lot of work to do.
You're gonna get new music skills.
you're gonna find your sound.
create your own style.
Holler!
And figure out
who you want to be as artists.
but most of all have fun!
And drum roll. please.
For the first time.
we're gonna be joined at camp
by a very special celebrity instructor.
I don't want to waste my summer
at some camp.
I'm Shane Gray. for crying out loud.
Hey. man. we used to love this place.
Three years ago we were campers.
Yeah. man.
this is where Connect 3 connected.
And you get to see your Uncle Brown.
Not a selling point.
Look. man. right now
you're the bad boy to the press.
And the label has a problem with that.
Which means
we have a problem with that.
Actually. I don't really have a problem
with that.
We have a problem with that.
This camp thing is supposed to fix it.
It's good P.R.. so do your time.
Enjoy the fresh air. Get a tan.
Oh. and can you make me a birdhouse
or something?
One word. payback.
That's two words.
By the way. we told the press
you'd be recording a duet
with the winner of Final Jam.
What?
- Shane! What's the haps. man?
- Hey. What's up. Uncle Brown?
Yeah.
I hear there's an open mike tonight.
Are you gonna sing?
In front of all those people? No way.
Sweetie. I hear you in your room.
You're really good. Mom's Honor.
And if you're nervous. so what?
Everyone is nervous.
That's why I'm making
so much food tonight.
'cause people eat
when they're nervous.
Not me. I don't think
I can eat another burger ever.
Okay. Why don't you go
take the trash out to the Dumpster
and then set up in the mess hall?
I'll finish up here.
You think you're hot
But I'm sorry you're not exactly
who you think you are
Can't tell you what
What you haven't got
But when we walk into the room
Once again from the top. girls.
You think you're hot
But I'm sorry you're not exactly
Who you think you are
Can't tell you what
What you haven't got
But when we walk into the room
Work with me here. people!
Hello? We're trying. but you...
If we want to win.
you guys have to listen to me.
Let's go again.
You think you're hot
But I'm sorry you're not exactly
Who you think you are
Can't tell you what
What you haven't got
But when we walk into...
Come on. guys. I learned my lesson.
I showered in cold water.
I have looked at a tree.
It's been three hours.
I need hair product.
I guess it's time
to embrace the natural look.
Oh. have fun.
Guys.
There he is!
Where'd he go?
Do you know what it's like
To feel so in the dark
To dream about a life
Where you're the shining star
Even though it seems
Like it's too faraway
I have to believe in myself
It's the only way
This is real. this is me
I'm exactly
Where I'm supposed to be now
Gonna let the light shine on me
Now I've found who I am
There's no way to hold it in
No more hiding who I want to be
I think he went that way.
This is me
Hello?
Who's in here?
There you are. sweetie.
I've got all the food set up.
so you. princess. are free.
Got to find something to wear.
Honey. it's camp.
It's not a fashion show.
Have you seen these kids?
They have a lot.
My usual is not going to cut it.
Oh. I think you look cute.
in a non-mom way.
Totally.
This. this is safe.
It's also mine.
Honey. wear your own clothes.
You'll be fine.
Be yourself.
Oh. those are pretty.
Hey. Caitlyn.
Hey. Mitchie. This is Lola.
Lola. Mitchie.
So. is this your first year?
- Yeah. Any advice?
- You're gonna love it here.
And this year. I hear the food
is supposed to be better.
Let's hope.
Hey. Camp Rockers!
Next up. let's have
a big Camp Rock welcome
for Lola Scott!
Wish me luck.
Who's got what it takes to be my guy
What it takes to make me shine
What it takes to get me fired up?
Who's got what it takes to be my beau
What it takes to make me glow
What it takes to make this beat flow?
Everyone talks about
What they think they need
They making up a list of things
One. two. three
Everyone is different
but where we can agree
Every girl wants her boy
To treat her sweet
Don't think that being mean
Will get you anywhere
Don't think that acting cool
Will make me wanna care
I need your respect
if you're gonna be the one
And if you must apply
Then try to get the job done
Who's got what it takes to be my guy
What it takes to make me shine
What it takes to get me fired up?
Who's got what it takes to be my beau
What it takes to make me glow
What it takes to make this beat flow?
I've been contemplating
What it takes
To make me give my heart
Could you be the one?
Standing in the crowd
I'm waiting to find out
I'm waiting. waiting. waiting. oh
Who's got what it takes to be my guy
What it takes to make me shine
What it takes to get me fired up?
Who's got what it takes to be my beau
What it takes to make me glow
What it takes to make this beat flow?
Wow! She's amazing!
Yeah. she should be.
Her mom's on Broadway.
Broadway? Wow.
Yeah. but the kids around here
don't care about that.
It's all about the bling.
That's why Tess over there
runs this camp.
Great. Something wicked
this way comes.
Hey. Caitlyn.
Your folks still wowing them
on the cruise ship?
- Actually they work in...
- Hi. I'm Mitchie.
Oh. hi. I'm Tess Tyler.
- I know. Wow. I love your mom.
- Of course you do.
I'm Mitchie Torres.
Hey. is your dad Nicky Torres.
the composer?
My dad staged one of his shows.
No.
- So what does he do?
- He owns a hardware store.
But my mom...
- Yeah?
- What?
The president of Hot Tunes TV.
In China.
Yeah. it's a huge market over there.
- Wow. Cool.
- So cool.
Major cool!
Okay. so have you met anybody?
Yeah. like everybody.
Last summer I was in. like.
three music videos.
Yeah. but. I mean.
you could hardly see me.
I was in the back.
- Wow.
Are you guys thinking
what I'm thinking?
- Of course.
- Absolutely.
What are we thinking?
There's an extra bed in our cabin.
It's yours if you want it.
- Really?
- Totally.
We're gonna be great friends.
Come on. sit with us in the VIP section.
I'm good. Thanks for asking.
Can you believe
not one of the cookbooks
has a recipe for chili for 300?
You don't need a recipe.
Everyone loves your food. It's official.
- Really?
- Camper's honor.
So. how was Opening Night Jam?
Did you sing?
No. But I met some girls.
and they want me
to move into their cabin.
And I know I have to help
in the kitchen.
but I'll just get up earlier
and meet you here.
Sweetie. of course you can move
into the cabin.
It'll be fine.
I got to get back to these cookbooks
'cause I got a rep to protect.
Peggy! Could you please stop that?
I can't hear.
Guys.
Which color?
Ella. they're exactly the same.
So you see my dilemma!
Mom? Hey. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm totally settled in.
Guess what? Shane Gray is...
Yeah. Yeah.
you can totally call me back.
Love you. too.
Have a good concert.
As usual.
What. Tess?
Hey. guys.
- Hey. Mitchie.
- Hey.
So. which bed is mine?
That one.
- But...
- Peggy doesn't mind. Do you?
I guess not.
One bag?
You can't possibly have all your clothes
in there.
Right. Well. I threw a lot
of my clothes away.
Yeah. I just got tired of them.
And you kept this?
Yeah. well. it came from China.
A little boutique called Shing Sha Ji.
- Wow.
- Totally wow.
What does that mean?
Happy summer.
Yeah. that store is the bomb.
Wow! Really cool bracelet.
It's from my mom.
Every time she wins a Grammy.
she adds a charm.
Love it. Totally blingalicious.
So. is that your diary?
No. My songs.
You write songs?
Yeah. but they're probably
not that good.
Come on.
Well. I bet they are good.
Let's hear one.
- No.
- Why not? We're friends now. right?
Yeah. Okay.
This is real. this is me
I'm exactly
where I'm supposed to be now
Gonna let the light shine on...
Yeah. it's not really that good.
What? That was totally good.
Right. Tess?
Totally.
What the...
Mitchie?
You're dreaming.
You're a rock princess.
Okay. I rock.
Subtitle | www.movieddl.me
Hey! Plenty of room over here.
mi a more.
- Yuck. You're going to chase her away.
- As usual.
- Good morning.
- Hey. guys.
- Hey.
- What's up?
Slumming. I see.
- What?
- Hey. Mitchie. Over here.
You better go. The queen awaits.
Your music. Are you any good?
I don't know. Maybe. Kind of.
Word of advice.
You wanna be friends with Tess.
don't be.
Mitchie.
See you around.
What happened to you this morning?
Um...
Early riser.
Yum. Toast.
- What?
- Rise and shine. superstar.
- Don't make me do this. Shane.
- Go away.
- Hey!
- Oh. sorry.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Fine. I'm up. okay? I'm up.
All right. We've both got classes
to teach. Yours starts in five.
And you might wanna put that mattress
out in the sun.
It's the only one you're gonna get.
Can you put some water in that vase?
Flowers look parched.
Four minutes!
Whoa!
If the class is a-rocking.
I'm-a glad I came knocking.
So. let's hear
what I'm working with this year.
- Who wants to sing first?
- Oh! Oh!
My goodness.
All right. Eeny. meeny. miny. you.
Me?
Can't argue with the finger.
I'll do it.
No. The finger picked her.
Well...
Okay.
Right. Let her rip.
Who will I be? It's up to me...
All right. I know you're singing a solo.
but it's so low. I can't hear you.
All right? So. bit louder.
Who will I be? It's up to me
All the never-ending possibility
That I can see
There's nothing that I can't do
Who will I be?
Yes. I believe I get to make the future
What I want to
If I can become anyone
and know the choice is up to me
Who will I be?
She's great.
- That was great.
- That was so amazing.
That's not bad. Not bad at all.
Is that an original?
Yeah. but it's mine. but...
No buts. It's good.
Let me have a high five.
- Oh. thanks.
- All right.
I didn't know that you were
that good. You totally rocked it.
- Totally.
- Thanks.
So. I've been thinking.
and you have to sing with us
in Final Jam.
Your vocals in the background would
be. like. amazing.
And we never let people in our group.
But you? A must. So you want in?
Well. I was thinking about singing solo
for Final Jam.
Solo in your first Final Jam?
That's brave.
You'll be fine.
Well. of course she'll be fine.
It's just that. I know how nervous I get.
Well. I'm sure I'll be nervous
at first. but...
In front of all those people.
but. yeah. you'll be fine.
- You've done it before.
- Done what before?
You've never sang
in front of an audience?
Well. yeah. I mean. choir.
I mean. I was never lead or anything.
and I was sort of in the back.
but it's still an audience.
Wow. You are brave.
Come on. girls. Let's get started.
Well. maybe a group would be better.
If you think so.
Yeah. No. it'll be fun. I want to.
- If you're sure.
- I'm totally sure.
- I gotta run.
- Where?
No. I mean. I got to call my mom.
China time.
Okay. okay. So. here's what...
- Sorry. I'm late.
- Oh. That's okay. honey.
The last batch of cookies
is in the oven.
You can start cleaning up.
I'm gonna take these down
to the storage room.
Hello?
I can hear you.
Hi.
Do you work here?
Yes.
Wow. You really get into your work.
I'm Shane.
But I'm sure
even the kitchen help knows that.
- Of course. It's nice to meet you.
- Actually. it's not so nice.
See. my manager said he sent over
my food allergy list.
but since I couldn't even go near
my breakfast this morning...
- Can I just talk to whoever's in charge?
- Excuse me?
What?
Well. you're kind of being a jerk.
- And you are?
- A person!
And there's a way to talk to a person
and that's not it.
Well. I'll have my manager
send it over again.
Fine.
Thank you?
Much better.
Yeah. I like that.
I don't need a chaperone. Unc.
Seeing how you blew off
your class yesterday. you sort of do.
I didn't sign up for this.
- Get my agent on the phone.
- "Get my agent"?
What happened to you. man?
That kid on that TV.
that's not who you really are.
In there. Shane.
What happened to the kid
who just loved music?
- He grew up.
- Big whoop!
Stop acting like it's all about you.
In my world. it is.
Oh. look. We're in my world.
And in my world. you're considered
an instructor at this camp.
which means you've got to instruct.
Starting with hip-hop dance at 2:00.
And five. six. seven. eight.
Okay. you guys. Remember.
when he gets here. act cool.
Wait. when who gets here?
Shane.
Wait. he's teaching this class?
Great.
Wait. is that flour in your hair?
No. No. it's Chinese body powder.
Pretty cool. huh?
Grab a mike and a hat.
Follow me if you can.
Hurry.
Let's go.
Yeah
First stop hit the groove
Let the music play
Next stop yeah everybody
It's time to celebrate
Here we go so let your flow show
Make the dreams you got become real
Across the floor.
Let's do this. let me hear you now
Show me how you feel
Let's start. start. start the party
Come on. come on. everyone
Let's sta-sta-start the party
What you waiting for now?
Start. start. start the party
Come on. come on live it up
Let's sta-sta-start the party
Everyone circle. Face the front.
I know you're never gonna wanna stop
Let the music take us to paradise
Let's close our eyes
Feel the groove wanna shake us
Everywhere and everybody turn it up
Let's start the party
Party
Gonna have a good night
Let's start. start. start the party
Come on. come on. everyone
Let's sta-sta-start the party
Crisscross.
What you waiting for now?
Start. start. start the party
Come on. come on. live it up
Let's sta-sta-start the party
I know you're never gonna wanna
Come on let me hear you holler
Party's never ever gonna stop
Talk about dancing to the beat
of a different drum.
You any good on the drums?
Man. you're a drummer. dude.
The drummer controls the beat.
The rhythm's in your hands.
Yeah. I guess.
Now we just have to work on getting
that beat from those sticks
to those feet.
Where were you this morning?
- Oh. no.
- Hi. girls.
Hi.
Hi. So. yummy breakfast.
Oh. How would you know?
There's hardly anything on your plate.
Morning carbs. definite no-no.
Yeah.
Well. I just wanted
to meet Mitchie's new friends.
This is Ella. Peggy. and Tess.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Well. I see you girls are really busy.
so I'll talk to you later.
Okay. Do you know her?
Yeah. don't you?
She's cooked for everybody
from Jessica and Nick pre-breakup
to Pharrell.
Really?
Yeah. I'm shocked
the camp even got her.
You mean. Jessica ate these eggs?
Yeah.
That's cool.
- It's like your old stuff.
- Yeah.
I was thinking the group can change up
our sound.
Do some different stuff.
So you coming up to the campfire?
Yeah. right.
All right. Well. you sit in here
by yourself. superstar.
'Cause you're right. Way cooler.
So. your friends. they seem nice.
Tess is interesting.
I know. but she's better
once you get to know her.
Yeah? And have you?
Have you gotten to know her?
Yeah. I guess.
I don't know. She just doesn't seem
like she's your type. you know.
- You've always been so...
- Invisible.
I was going to say independent.
Hurry up and finish those potatoes
if you wanna get to the campfire.
So we call this the Campfire Jam.
It's about expression.
The freedom to be
who you really wanna be.
Hit it!
I'm too cool for my dress
These shades don't leave my head
Everything you say is so irrelevant
You follow and I lead
You wanna be like me
But you're just a wannabe
Love it or hate it
Me. myself. and I agree
You'll never catch up with me
'Cause I'm too cool
Too cool
Yeah. I'm too cool to know you
Don't take it personal
Don't get emotional
You know it's the truth
I'm too cool for you
You think you're hot
But I'm sorry you're not exactly
who you think you are
Can't tell you what
What you haven't got
But when we walk into the room
I'm too cool for you
You see some are born
With beauty brains and talent
And they got it all
While others have to try all their lives
Still they never get the call
That's the difference
between you and me
Obviously
I'm a natural. I'm the real deal
I can't help the way I am
Hope you don't misunderstand
But I'm too cool
Too cool
Yeah. I'm too cool to know you
Don't take it personal
Don't get emotional
You know it's the truth
I'm too cool for you
Did you enjoy singing backup?
Can't a guy get some peace?
Sorry.
- Sorry.
- You said that already.
I'm sorry. I...
Was that you playing?
It sounded kind of different.
Than my usual stupid cookie-cutter
pop star stuff?
- Sorry to disappoint.
- You didn't.
I liked it.
I mean. it was good
for stupid cookie-cutter pop star stuff.
Wow. you really know
how to make a guy feel better.
I thought you loved your sound.
You created it.
- You're like a Camp Rock legend.
- Some legend.
I only played the music
that the label thinks will sell. That's it.
You don't think that song would sell?
I don't know.
Well. you'll never know if you don't try.
And. by the way. I know of one girl
that would buy that song.
Oh. I'm so sorry!
Actually. I'm so not.
I would respond. but...
But you are responding
by saying that you're not responding.
Shut up.
Okay. that was on purpose.
Doesn't matter.
Anything makes that outfit look better.
See?
Okay.
- Nice. Caitlyn.
- Good shot.
Stop. Hey. no. you guys. stop!
- Stop.
- My spaghetti slipped.
I can't believe you did that!
Neither can I.
Busted.
I hate when I have to be uncool.
Lay it on me.
- She's always been jealous of me...
- She's impossible.
...and she cannot stand the fact
that I'm probably to win Final Jam.
- so she spilled...
- Whoa!
Enough. Make it plain.
Who was the first one to throw food?
That's easy. Caitlyn.
- That's technically true. but...
- No buts.
Since you wanna play with food.
I can hook you up
with a job this summer.
From here on out.
you're on kitchen duty.
What? I mean...
Ew.
- But...
- Again with the buts.
Look. it's settled.
Happy cooking.
Thanks a lot.
- Oh!
- You hungry?
Just a little bit.
Do you have a second?
Um...
- Sure.
- I wanna run something by you.
Every time I think
I'm closer to the heart
Of what it means to know
Just who I am
I think I finally found
A better place to start
But no one ever seems to understand
I need to try to get to where you are
Could it be you're not that far?
You're the voice I hear inside my head
The reason that I'm singing
I need to find you
I got to find you
You're the missing piece
I need the song inside of me
I need to find you
I got to find you
I've been feeling lost
Can't find the words to say
Spending all my time
Stuck in yesterday
Where you are is where I wanna be
Oh. next to you. and you next to me
Oh. I need to find you
You're the voice I hear inside my head
The reason that I'm singing
I need to find you
I got to find you
You're the missing piece
I need the song inside of me
I need to find you
I got to find you
Wow.
I heard this girl singing.
and it kind of reminded me
of the music that I liked.
So I started playing around
with some chords. and...
- I know it's not finished. but...
- No. No. it's good.
It's really good. And I don't lie.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I don't know.
You seem different.
Good different.
Yeah. Definitely different.
So. I better get going.
Back to the kitchen?
- What?
- To get some dip for these chips?
Oh!
Yeah. Yeah. Right.
Hey. Mom. how you doing?
I'm all right. How are you?
I am great.
I'm wonderful. I'm fantastic. I'm...
- Putting chips into bowls...
- Right.
Hey. Mrs. Torres.
Hi. Caitlyn. Thanks for coming in early.
Taco Night takes
the entire kitchen staff
and our six hands.
Six?
Yeah. My daughter.
So can you please start in
on the onions?
Brown wants to talk to me
about next week's campfire pig-out.
Sure.
Hey! You must be hands five and six.
I didn't know Connie had a daughter.
I'm Caitlyn.
Do you need some help?
Mitchie?
Wait a minute.
You're the cook's daughter.
She's your mom.
Oh. this is rich.
But apparently you're not.
So what are you waiting for. huh?
Run. Go tell everybody.
- Maybe I should.
- Fine. Whatever.
How long did you think
you could keep your little secret?
Longer than this.
Why?
- Why do you care?
- Oh. I don't.
But when I tell everybody.
I want the whole backstory.
I just wanted to fit in. okay?
I think your whole charade is stupid
and immature.
You're hiding behind some crazy lie.
What about you. huh? You hide. too!
The whole
"I don't care about anything" attitude?
Well. if you don't care.
why are you here?
What happened to you?
She got drowned in her lies.
What. Caitlyn?
Nothing.
- Caitlyn. wait!
- No. no. no. no. You can talk later.
First you got to get out
of these wet clothes. Come on.
Says here in this magazine
I'm Shane's type.
It's just a matter of time.
"Warm. funny. talented."
You? I don't get it.
- Hey. guys. what are you doing?
- The question is. what were you doing?
- You're always AWOL.
- What?
Hey. Mitchie. I was thinking.
After camp. maybe we could come
to visit you and your mom in China
and go to that Happy Summer store.
Sure. My mom would like that.
Okay. guys.
Tonight is the Pajama Jam.
So. outfit check.
White shorts and green hoodies.
What? Green is Shane's favorite color.
It was in the magazine.
- All right!
- The other lemmings are over there.
- Look. Caitlyn. about what...
- Save it. Mitchie.
If that's even your real name.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Are we ready?
Where are your T-shirt and shorts?
Yeah. I thought that we were supposed
to wear the same thing?
The backup singers should wear
the same thing.
Not the lead singer. hello!
Next. give it up for the awesome
Caitlyn Geller!
And this is in honor
of you awesome Camp Rockers.
She's really good.
Hey. Shane likes her. too.
Help! Help. there's a snake! Snake!
It's just the power cord
to the sound system. Tess.
Oh. Right. My bad.
- You are so full of it!
- What?
You can't stand
that people might actually like
what other people do.
Okay. What is that?
She said. "Whatever. major loser."
Oh. wow. Tess.
"Whatever. major loser?"
That is so last year.
I mean. everyone knows that.
Oh. well. I guess not everyone.
Hey! Does this look like a record. girls?
Huh?
I mean. a CD.
Does this cookie look like a CD?
'Cause I want it to look authentic
next to my eighth note cupcakes.
Everything looks great. Connie.
These theme nights are so busy. huh?
Oh. I gotta go get the ice cream
for my Rolling Stone cones!
See you later.
So. did you sign up for Final Jam?
Yeah.
So. what are you thinking about doing?
This is freaking me out.
Why are we talking?
I don't know. Maybe I'm slumming?
Or maybe I wanted to set
you up for that!
My gosh.
So. thank you for yesterday. but...
Hey. I always stick up for my friends.
It's fun being friends with Tess.
How would you know?
Because I was friends with Tess.
I know. it's hard to believe.
More like impossible. What happened?
Tess doesn't like competition.
and she felt I was.
See. with her. there can only be
one star. Herself.
Look. I know it's fun being
friends with her.
She can make you feel so important
and she's popular. but so what?
Oh. come on.
Being popular is so not a "so what."
No. there are perks.
Like... Well. like...
Like singing backup to Tess
all the time?
Like never getting to say
what you really feel?
Oh. and those exciting short outfits?
Those were real high points.
You're right. Sell your soul.
Hey. I'm on your side.
Oh. shoot.
I was supposed to go meet up with...
We're practicing for Final Jam.
Of course. Her Highness awaits.
Hand-clapping.
hip-shaking...
Hello?
Hey. buddy.
how's my birdhouse coming?
- Jason!
- Sorry. It's not my fault
you didn't ask him to
make you anything.
- I didn't want anything.
- Well. I wanted a birdhouse! So what?
And what do you need a birdhouse for?
Because I wanted to see
more birds in...
Guys. Guys.
Sorry.
Listen. About me recording
with a camper.
- You gotta do it. man. No go-backs.
- Yeah. No go-backs.
It's. like. the Golden Rule.
No. dude. the Golden Rule
is "Tell the truth."
Dude. then it can be. like.
the Silver Rule.
- Why is it the Silver Rule?
- Okay. fine. the Copper Rule.
- The Copper Rule?
- Well. give me tin at least.
Guys.
- Sorry.
Listen. I've been thinking about
the whole recording thing.
and I think it's really cool.
Are you getting too much sun?
'Cause we can bring you a hat
when we come to visit.
I'm fine. And remember. whoever wins.
no go-backs. See you guys Saturday.
Now I just have to find that girl
with the voice.
Hey. Andy! Buddy.
You wanna do me a favor?
Sure.
Shane Gray is looking for the girl
with the voice.
Start. start. start the party
Come on. come on. everyone
Let's sta-sta-start the party
What you waiting for now?
Let's start. let's start
Let's start the party
-Hey
- Come on. come on. live it up
Let's start-start-start the party
I know you're never gonna wanna stop
Let's start. start. start the party
Come on. come on. everyone
What you waiting for now?
Start. start. start the party
Come on. come on. everyone
Let's start. start
What you waiting for?
Here we go so let your flow show
Make the dreams you have
become real
Let's do this. let me hear you
Show me how you feel
Start. start. start the party
Come on. come on. everyone
Let's start. start. start the party
I know you're never gonna wanna stop
Let the music take us to paradise
Let's close our eyes
Feel the groove
Wanna shake us
Aren't you gonna get in line?
Oh. it's not me. Trust.
Anyway. he's never heard me sing.
Turn on that radio
As loud as it can go
Gotta dance until my feet
can't feel the ground
So. does your voice sound better
over here?
Why don't we get in one of these things
and you can tell me.
- Really?
- Yeah. It was awesome.
Yeah.
I don't think
we're doing this right.
What? You don't like going in circles?
So. have you found
your special girl yet?
Why? Are you jealous?
- Jerk.
- Hey.
Being a jerk is a part
of the rock star image.
Keeping up an image can be tiring.
But it keeps the posers away.
I never know if people are hanging with
me for the free stuff or for the parties.
Oh. Definitely the free stuff.
Funny.
Come on.
I know you're really not a jerk.
I mean. you're helping Andy
with his dancing.
and those screaming girls
seem to like you.
Which brings me back
to the whole jealous thing.
I take that back. You are a jerk.
- It must be the same for you. too. huh?
- What?
Because of your mom.
and her job at Hot Tunes.
People probably are always
fake around you.
Yeah. Right. Totally.
You know. it's nice talking
to someone who gets it.
Yeah. Me. too.
Seriously. Mom.
Okay. we're done with the dishes.
Okay. girls. have fun at the campfire.
- Okay. Bye.
- Thanks.
- I love you. Mom.
- Love you. too. Bye!
- Hey. gang.
- We love you. Brown!
Whoa! All right. all right. Kids.
Okay. score.
I finally talked my nephew
into singing us a song!
Shane. rock the camp!
Hey. guys. I got a surprise for you.
Guys. come on out.
So we're gonna play something new.
Let us know what you think.
Music
I turn on that radio
As loud as it can go
Wanna dance until my feet
can't feel the ground
Can't feel the ground
Say goodbye to all my fears
One good song. they disappear
And nothing in the world
can bring me down
Can bring me down
Hand-clapping
Hip-shaking
Heartbreaking
There's no faking
What you feel
when you ride it home. yeah
Music's in my soul
I can hear it
Every day
And every night
It's the one thing on my mind
Music's got control
And I'm never letting go. no. no
I just wanna play my music
Music
Got my six-string on my back
Don't need anything but that
Everything I want is here with me
Here with me
So forget that fancy car
I don't need to go that far
And what's driving me is
following my dreams. yeah
Hand-clapping
Earth-shaking
Heartbreaking
There's no faking
What you feel
When you're on a roll
Yeah. yeah
Music's in my soul
I can hear it
Every day
And every night
It's the one thing on my mind
Music's got control
And I'm never letting go. no. no
I just wanna play my music
Can't imagine what it'd be like
What it'd be like
Without the sound of all my heroes
singing all my favorite songs
So I can sing along
Music's in my soul
I can hear it
Every day
Every night
It's the one thing on my mind
Music's got control
And I'm never letting go. no. no
I just wanna play my music
Music's in my soul
I can hear it
Every day
And every night
It's the one thing on my mind
Music's got control
And I'm never letting go. no. no
I just wanna play my music
All night long
Yeah!
Man. they loved it. You were right.
I know I was right. What did I do?
Not you. Shane.
The label has to let us do this.
They won't. Look at what they made us
call the band.
Yeah! How can we do that?
If we hit the studio tonight. we can
get them a demo by tomorrow.
I mean. they can't say no
once they hear this.
They can't?
Guys. I can't just leave.
I'm not finished here yet.
All right. man. Do what you gotta do.
We are talking about finishing
my birdhouse. right?
- Come on! See you at Final Jam.
- Bye.
...off the chain. That was so great.
That was the best song ever.
It was so great.
- That was so amazing. And...
- I know. he was so...
Did you see them?
Hey. Mitchie.
Tell us about your mom again.
Her mom is a great person.
What's your mom like?
She's like a mom.
I mean. I know she's the president
of Hot Tunes TV China.
but tell me again about
how important she is.
She...
I'm sorry. What?
She's pretty cool.
And...
And she's not the president
of Hot Tunes TV China.
What's that? She's not president?
You mean. you lied to everybody?
No. I was...
So. she's what? A vice president?
Treasurer?
Tess.
Shut up. Go on. Tell us.
No.
- She's a cook.
- A cook?
At Hot Tunes China.
No.
Here.
So you lied.
Your mom cooks our food.
and you help her.
That's the only way you could
afford this camp. right?
You're a real jerk.
Maybe. But at least
I'm not a big. fat liar.
Come on. guys.
Mitchie.
Mitchie has dishes to do. Let's go.
Shane.
- You were lying all summer?
- Yes. but I...
You know. I'm so used to
people pretending around me.
- I was not pretending!
- And I really thought you were different.
But you're just like everyone else.
You wanted to be friends
with Shane Gray. not me.
- Trick's on me. huh?
- I was just trying...
Save it for your interview
with Pop Informer magazine.
I know I gave you an earful.
Not here. you don't. Come on.
So what exactly happened last night?
Nothing.
Didn't look like nothing to me. mate.
You look crushed.
Pummeled. Absolutely destroyed.
I got it. Uncle Brown.
Look. whatever.
I'm just gonna focus on my music.
Change my sound.
I don't wanna get sidetracked
with liking someone anyway.
You still looking for that girl?
What?
I'm plugged into the
camp gossip. mate.
It's crazy.
I have her song stuck in my head.
This is real
This is me
I'm exactly where
I'm supposed to be now
Gonna let the light
"This is real. this is me.
"I'm exactly where I'm supposed to be.
"Gonna let the light shine on me."
Mitchie. you are so never
going to see Final Jam.
What a joke.
"I hope you
don't misunderstand. I'm just too cool."
You know? I mean.
"I'm like too over you."
You know what I mean?
Hey. guys. Have a seat.
So. Final Jam is coming up.
and I know you're all very excited.
Yeah! You know it!
So here's some advice.
It's not all about your image.
None of it means anything unless
people see who you really are.
And your music has to be
who you really are.
It's gotta show how you feel.
Or it doesn't mean anything.
I didn't know you felt so ashamed
of yourself.
I'm not ashamed.
It's just. for once. I just wanted
to fit in and be popular.
What do you mean?
You have plenty of friends at home.
I have one. And the last time I checked.
no one was busting their butts
to sit next to us at the lunch table.
And when I got here I just...
I just wanted it to be different.
You know? Just once.
My sweetie. you are so much
more than you can see.
You don't have to lie about
who or what you are.
I'm not just saying it
'cause I'm your mom!
Mom.
Okay. I admit I'm a little bit biased.
But it is so true. You are talented.
Your music speaks to people.
People wanna listen to you.
And it is not just me and your dad.
That's what I said.
- That was funny.
- I know. I want to do that.
Hey. guys. Can I sit with you?
I guess.
But you have to give me your cake.
Okay. deal.
You know. sitting with the kitchen help
is really hurting my rep.
What rep?
Believe me. it's probably not that funny.
The chicken was kind of dry.
Could you tell your mom to be
just a little more careful?
Tess!
Stop talking to me like that.
Stop talking to everyone like that.
I may be the cook's daughter.
and my father may not be rich.
but I'm a much better person than
someone who feels good about herself
because she makes everyone
else feel bad.
And I'll take that any day.
If it wasn't obvious.
you're so out of the group.
Then we'll make our own group.
- I don't know why this is so fascinating.
- I don't think you're doing that right.
- Wait. Look. I'm a pro.
- Don't get it in my macaroni.
I'm sure they have it!
Okay. she has officially lost it.
No. I didn't lose anything.
You guys stole it.
- What?
- What's going on here?
Tess thinks that Mitchie and Caitlyn
stole her charm bracelet.
What?
I'm sorry. Brown. but these girls
would never do such a thing.
Yeah. Look. let's just settle this. right?
But...
I know it was her. She was lying
all summer about who she is.
Who knows what else she'd lie about?
- Now. wait a minute.
- Mom. don't.
If she wants to look. let her.
This is stupid.
Okay. look. let me just scope this out.
and then I'll have a quick look
in your cabin. Right?
- Fine.
- Whatever.
You're not gonna find anything.
'cause I didn't...
That's it. That is my charm bracelet.
There's gotta be some mistake.
Like what?
I snuck into the kitchen and...
Tess. I got this. All right?
I am totally wigged-out.
Yeah. So are we.
I'm not.
Well. rules are rules.
and since it's the end of camp.
I have no choice.
I've gotta ban you guys
from the rest of camp activities.
until the end of Final Jam.
We didn't do anything. She's lying.
- Do you have any proof?
- No. but...
Well. then I'm sorry. My hands are tied.
Until the end of Final Jam.
Camper mates. and matettes.
I am holding the lineup for Final Jam.
I am gonna pin it up on the wall.
Let me get out of the room before
you all come and have a look at it.
All right! Goodness me.
This is so not fair.
I know.
Guess who?
Dude. you're in the room.
I can see you.
I can see you. too. man.
I've missed you.
Group hug.
Much better. It hasn't been
the same just hugging Nate.
Yeah. it hasn't been.
So. good news.
The press is here and they're gonna
cover the whole night.
- The label loves it.
- That's awesome!
Hey. man. where's this amazing singer
you've been looking for?
What? I know things.
Hoping to find her tonight.
This was supposed to be a fun summer
that was all about music.
and all I did was get caught up
in Tess drama.
It happens.
I can't believe I agreed to be
some background singer
just because I got intimidated.
That's what Tess can do to you.
No. I did it to me.
I've never seen Brown so harsh.
I know. He just kept repeating
"Until the end of Final Jam."
I know. I was there.
What?
Come on! Let's go! Let's go!
Okay. Who's stoked? Yeah!
All right! All right!
Yeah!
Okay. campers. friends. family.
Camp Rock fans. this is it.
Tonight music history will be made
as Camp Rock finds
a new Final Jam winner!
Five. six. seven. eight.
Come on.
come on. come on
Look at me
This is not amateur night.
This is serious.
We did it right!
No! You didn't. You never do!
I'm trying to win here.
You guys may be used to losing.
but not me.
I'm tired of picking up the slack.
Stop telling us what to do!
You're the one
who's ruining everything.
You're too intense all the time.
and I am sick and tired
of picking up your slack. too!
Peggy. come back here!
Who needs her?
She was holding us back.
Now you really better not mess up.
You know what? Don't worry about me.
Do it yourself. I'm done.
BTW. your lip gloss is
so not glossy anymore.
All right.
This year. the Final Jam winner
will not only get a Camp Rock trophy
and a big one. I might add.
he or she is gonna get a sweet prize.
a chance to record with my nephew.
pop star Shane Gray!
Yes! All right! Give it up! All right!
To make sure
the right camper is chosen.
we've invited the other members
of Connect 3 to be judges.
Yes!
Thank you so much.
All right.
Okay. Put your hands together
for Barron James.
Sander Lawyer. and
the Hasta La Vista Crew.
Yeah. it's your boy Barry
And the place to be is crazy
Come rock with me
Couldn't wait to leave
But now I hate to go
Last day at camp
Packing my bags slow
Made so many friends
Why does it have to end
In the end it's a win
'Cause we grown so close together
Remember when we first met. first day
Thinking this would be no fun
No way
Way
Now it's time to leave
Leave
But now we wanna stay
Stay
Stay. stay. stay. stay. stay. oh
Hasta la vista
I'm-a gonna say goodbye to you
Whatever happens I'll be cool with you
Wanna give me your number?
I'm-a call you
Promise I won't forget you
Hasta la vista
We'll all be going separate ways
Say everything you didn't say
This is your moment
Before you go
Come on now
Get up and show them
Keep doing your thing. thing. thing
Yeah.
So hot
Get a clap to this
H-A-S-T-A
La vista
Hasta la vista
I'm-a gonna say goodbye to you
Whatever happens I'll be cool with you
Hey!
Wanna give me your number?
I'm-a call you
Promise I won't forget you
Hasta la vista
We'll all be going separate ways
Say everything you didn't say
This is your moment
Before you go
Come on now
Get up and show them
H-A-S-T-A
La vista
Hasta la vista
Oh. my goodness! Okay!
Now. let's give it up for a group that
has the "it" factor. whatever "it" is.
The It Girls!
Mom?
Wake up
When will things be good enough
for you to see
All that we can be
I'm sick of
Playing games and acting like
we never care
That we're never there
We pay attention
For only seconds
Look at you. look at me
There's never any us
Can't you see all we can become
We can shine like the sun
If we believe that two stars
are brighter than one
Come on. come on. come on
Look at you
Is it too much to ask
That you put us first?
Oh
I feel like we're last in our universe
And that's not where we ought to be
Look at you. look at me
There's never any us
Can't you see all we can become
We can shine like the sun
If we believe that two stars
are brighter than one
Come on. come on. come on
Look at you
Look at me
Come on. come on. come on
Look at you
Well. it looks like we are
basically finished the...
Put it on pause.
We have a last-minute addition.
Come on up. Margaret Dupree!
Who's Margaret?
I am.
Go. Margaret!
They tell you a good girl is quiet and
That you should never ask why
'Cause it only makes it harder to fit in
And you should be happy. excited
Even if you're just invited
'Cause the winners need someone
to clap for them
It's so hard just waiting
In a line that never moves
It's time you started making
Your own rules
You gotta scream
until there's nothing left
With your last breath
Say here I am
Here I am
Make them listen
'Cause there's no way
you'll be ignored
Not anymore
Say here I am
Here I am
The world better make some room
Yeah. move over. over
'Cause you're coming through
You gotta scream
until there's nothing left
With your last breath
Here I am
Make them listen
'Cause there's no way
you'll be ignored
Not anymore
Say here I am
Here I am
Peggy?
What?
You were really good.
I didn't know you were that good.
and when someone's that good.
someone should tell them.
Thanks.
And I'm sorry.
Wow! She was amazing.
I know. I know.
All right. all right. all right. Settle down.
Settle down. sunshine!
I guess that's it.
It's officially the end of Final Jam.
and time for our judges to go off
in private. and. well. judge.
So. we'll check you in a minute.
Excuse me. Just a minute.
It's the end of Final Jam.
I was so hoping you'd catch on.
Now get out there. steal their hearts.
and rock it. poppet.
- Okay.
I've always been the kind of girl
That hid my face
So afraid to tell the world
What I've got to say
But I have this dream
Bright inside of me
I'm gonna let it show
It's time to let you know
To let you know
This is real. this is me
I'm exactly
where I'm supposed to be now
Gonna let the light shine on me
Now I've found who I am
There's no way to hold it in
No more hiding who I wanna be
This is me
That's the song!
So that must be the girl.
Do you know what it's like
You think?
To feel so in the dark
To dream about a life
Where you're the shining star
Even though it seems
Like it's too faraway
I have to believe in myself
It's the only way
This is real. this is me
I'm exactly where
I'm supposed to be now
Gonna let the light shine on me
Now I've found who I am
There's no way to hold it in
No more hiding who I wanna be
This is me
You're the voice I hear inside my head
The reason that I'm singing
I need to find you
I gotta find you
You're the missing piece I need
The song inside of me
-I need to find you
- I need to find you
-I gotta find you
- I gotta find you
This is real. this is me
I'm exactly where
I'm supposed to be now
Gonna let the light shine on me
Now I've found who I am
There's no way to hold it in
No more hiding who I wanna be
Yeah
-This is me
- You're the missing piece I need
The song inside of me
This is me. yeah
You're the voice I hear inside my head
The reason that I'm singing
Now I've found who I am
There's no way to hold it in
No more hiding who I wanna be
-This is me
- This is me
Yeah!
Okay. gang. this is it.
The winner of Final Jam this year is...
Drum roll. please.
Margaret Dupree! Yes!
You won! You won!
You gotta go! You gotta go!
Way to go. Margaret!
You just got yourself a chance
to record with Shane Gray! Yes!
Congratulations. Peggy.
You deserve it. You were amazing.
You did it! I mean. I did it. We did...
You guys were really great.
Thanks.
Yeah.
So. I told Brown you guys
didn't take my bracelet.
Wow.
Thank you.
See you next summer.
Sure.
Mitchie. You were fabulous.
Honey. I'm sorry you didn't win.
But I did. I won the best summer
of my life. Thanks to you.
I love you.
- We'll see you in a few. okay?
- Okay.
So I guess my search is over.
That depends on
who you're looking for.
Hi. I'm Mitchie.
I'm Shane.
You up for a canoe ride later?
I wouldn't miss it.
All right! Okay. Camp Rockers!
Final Jam is over.
and you know what that means?
My favorite part of the summer.
the Final Jam jam session!
Let's kick it!
'Cause we rock
We rock
We rock on
Oh. we rock. we rock on
Come as you are
You're a superstar
World's in your pocket and you know it
You can feel that beat
Running through your feet
Heart's racing fast
You're rock and rolling
All that you need is the music
To take you to some other place
Where you know you belong
Raise your hands up
in the air and scream
We're finding our voice
following our dreams
'Cause we rock. we rock
We rock. we rock on
Nobody in the world's
gonna bring us down
The louder we go
Well. the better we sound
'Cause we rock. we rock
We rock. we rock on
-We got the music in our souls
- The music in our souls
-And it's the thing we want the most
- What we want the most
It picks us up when we fall down
It turns our world around
We rock. we rock. we rock
Every day and every night
'Cause we rock. we rock
We rock. we rock on
It's all we wanna do in life
Raise your hands up in the air
and scream
We're finding our voice
Following our dreams
'Cause we rock. we rock
We rock. we rock on
Nobody in the world's
gonna bring us down
The louder we go
Well. the better we sound
'Cause we rock. we rock
We rock. we rock on
Raise your hands up in the air
and scream
We're finding our voice
Following our dreams
'Cause we rock. we rock
We rock. we rock on
Nobody in the world's
gonna bring us down
The louder we go
Well. the better we sound
'Cause we rock. we rock
We rock. we rock on
We rock. we rock. we rock on
We rock. we rock
Camp Rock
- Whoa.
- Wow.
Whoa.
- It's incredible.
- Awesome.
- Wow.
- So cool.
Caitlyn. we know you said you built
a little recording studio...
But this is the coolest thing I've seen
since my mom's tour bus.
Oh. Phenomenal!
Extraordinary.
Totally!
Way cool.
Way. way cool.
We still keep all our old stuff in here.
We got the skis and the bikes.
My dad's tools.
Okay. guys. I can't wait to get started.
- I know. Me. too.
- Oh. my God. We're gonna...
Okay. everybody. grab some mikes
and set them up.
I'm excited.
Okay. let me just adjust some things.
All right. get your headphones.
- Got them? Are we ready?
- Yeah.
- All right.
And go.
We're done. but it's not over
We'll start it again
After the end of the day
It keeps getting better
Don't be afraid
We'll do it together
Come on. come on
You know
It's your time to move
It's my time to move
Come on. come on
Let go
Leave it all behind
Your past and mine
Gone are the days of summer
We couldn't change it if we tried
But why would we want to
Let's go where we got to
Our paths will cross again in time
It's never the same tomorrow
And tomorrow's never clear
So come on. come on. you know
Our time
Our time is here
We know. but we're not certain
How can we be?
How can we see what's ahead?
The world keeps on turning
And all we can do
ls travel each day to the next
Come on. come on. you know
It's your time to move
It's my time to move
Come on. come on
Let go
Leave it all behind
Your past and mine
Gone are the days of summer
We couldn't change it if we tried
But why would we want to
Let's go where we got to
Our paths will cross again in time
It's never the same tomorrow
And tomorrow's never clear
So come on. come on. you know
Our time
Our time is here
Yeah
Come on. come on. come on
Our time is here
Gone are the days of summer
We couldn't change it if we tried
If we tried
So come on. come on. come on
Yeah. come on. come on. come on
So come on. come on. you know
Our time
Our time is here
Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah
Yeah. yeah
'Cause we rock
We rock. we rock on
All that you need is the music
To take you to some other place
Where you know you belong
Raise your hands up in the air
and scream
We're finding our voice
Following our dreams
'Cause we rock. we rock
We rock. we rock on
Nobody in the world's
gonna bring us down
The louder we go
Well. the better we sound
'Cause we rock. we rock
We rock. we rock on
We rock. we rock. we rock on
We rock. we rock
Camp Rock
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-